pgcps.org 2010-06-20

# PGCPS Privacy Policy

## Prince George’s County Public Schools Privacy Policy

Prince George's County Public Schools would like to thank you for visiting our web site.  We have provided you this page with important information about our web site privacy policy.

The Prince George's County Public School system web site exists to provide the general public and Prince George's County Students, Staff and Parents with the information about our school system along with tools to achieve our primary goal to provide a superior education to our students.

  **Web site management and support**

Web site management and support is provided by the Department of Television Resources and Web Services and the Division of Information Technology.  [www.pgcps.org](http://www.pgcps.org/) is managed by over 300 web managers who publish information to the 20,000 page web site.  All web sites must comply with the Acceptable Use Policy.

  **General Information Collection and Use**

The information typically collected from your visit to PGCPS (unless you voluntarily provide additional information) is the IP Address or Internet Protocol Address from the computer you are using, the pages you visited, and the web addresses you used to access the site.  Some sites in the pgcps.org domain use cookies to store temporary data (like the online employment site).  They expire when you leave the site.

PGCPS reserves the right to employ and review the results of software that searches, monitors, and/or identifies potential violations of the Acceptable Use Policy.

  **Personal Information Collection and Use**

Occasionally, schools and offices may request information from visitors to the pgcps.org site.  The information requests may be in the form of anonymous surveys, but may also extend to employment and volunteer applications as well as general contact forms where responses are necessary.  PGCPS maintains confidentiality of the data collected and the data will be used only for the purposes outlined in the application where it was collected.   It may be shared with appropriate staff.  PGCPS does not share of sell visitor information to any third parties.  Personally identifiable information about students is not considered public information.

  **Links outside[www.pgcps.org](http://www.pgcps.org/)**

The PGCPS Acceptable Use Policy states that web managers may link to any website deemed to support the administrative and educational goals of the school system.  Principals or administrators of the web sites are responsible for any link that is posted on their sites.
